If I jump into my computer
and I hear that
what's happening? All computers need to
get heat off the chip as quickly as
possible. It's called heat spreading and
find somewhere to dump it, a heat sink.
So, with that what's happening is your
chip is generating heat and the copper
on top is trying to get it off the chip
and spread it out and send it through
copper pipes and dump it into a bunch of
aluminum fins until the fan that you're
hearing blows across the fins large
surface area to finally carry the heat
out of the computer. This problem inside
your computer is a tiny example of a
huge heat problem that's holding [music]
back virtually all of our cutting edge
computers. And that's because most of
what's around me right now is made of
silicon. But [music] now there's a new
material we think might be able to help,
diamond. To see why, watch our longer
video and subscribe. [music]